https://www.chcu.org/privacy-policy/

Contact Us
Taking care of the financial needs of our members is our main objective every day.
Community Healthcare Credit Union is committed to providing its members low cost
friendly personal service while offering its members competitive lending rates.
Home Privacy Policy (current)
Privacy Disclosure Policy
The National Credit Union Association (NCUA) recently published its final ruling regarding disclosure of personal information about our members with any one other than those authorized by law (lawyers, credit bureaus, auditors, regulators, etc.) The rule is required under the Gramm-Leach Bliley Act, an act of Congress, which established rules governing the protection and disclosure of non-public personal financial information of consumers and customers of all financial institutions. In complying with the obligation to notify our members of this new ruling designed for your protection, we submit the following.
Community Healthcare Credit Union is owned by its members and run by a board of directors you elect. You can be confident that your financial privacy is the top priority of this credit union. We are required by law to give you this privacy notice to explain how we collect, use and safeguard your personal financial information. If you have any questions please contact a member service representative at (860) 643-3420 or write us at 48 Haynes Street, Manchester, CT.
We are committed to providing you with competitive products and services to meet your financial needs, which necessitates that we share information about you to complete your transactions. We may disclose all of the information we collect as described below, to companies that perform marketing or other services on our behalf, or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. To protect our member’s privacy, we work only with companies that agree to maintain strong confidentiality to protect and limit the use of information we provide to them.
Information we collect and disclose about you
We collect and may disclose non-public personal information about you from the following sources:
Information we receive from you on membership and loan applications and other forms
Information we receive about your transactions with us or others
Information we receive from a consumer-reporting agency
Information obtained when verifying the information you provide on an application or other forms. Such may be from your current or past employer or from institutions where you conduct financial transactions.
We may also disclose information we collect about you under circumstances as permitted or required by law. These disclosures typically include information to process transactions on your behalf, to conduct the operations of our Credit Union, to follow instructions as you authorize, or to protect the security of our financial records.
If you terminate your membership with Community Healthcare Credit Union, we will not share information we have collected about you, except as permitted or required by law.
How do we protect your information?
We restrict access to non-public personal information about you to those credit union officials who have specific business purpose in utilizing your data. Our credit union officials are trained in the importance of maintaining confidentiality and member privacy. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations and leading industry practices to safeguard your non-public personal information.
OnlineBanking
Login
BillPay
Login
Visa CreditCard Online
Login
Pay yourCHCU Loan
Pay Now
You are now leaving Community Healthcare Credit Union's web site and are going to a web site that is
not
operated by the credit union. Community Healthcare Credit Union, Inc is not responsible for the
content or
availability of linked sites.
Please be advised that Community Healthcare Credit Union Inc does not represent either the third
party or you,
the member, if you enter into a transaction. Further, the privacy and security policies of the
linked site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Proceed
Close
Back
to top
